

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, machine reading comprehension and language model. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience _____

Data61, CSIRO Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY CONRAD SANDERSON

- Dec. 2020 Present
- Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a top conference paper in COLING 2020.

Monash Univeristy Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY REZA HAFFARI

- May. 2020 Present • Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a top conference paper in COLING 2020.

UNSW Sydney Sydney, Australia

CASUAL ACADEMIC Feb. 2020 - Present

- Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation
- Teaching in ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals

Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia Nov. 2019 - Sep. 2020

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY ARNE LAUCHT

- Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- Strongly recommended by Michael Wang

Project

Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- · Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Education

UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)

Sydney, Australia

Jul. 2018 - May. 2021(Expected)

Weighed Average Mark 87.2, Top 2% in Faculty of Engineering

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Extracurricular Activity

TERRY ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ JULY 14, 2020

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

POWER ENGINEER

Oct. 2019 - Present • Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.

• Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

May. 2019 - Present

Publication

Paper Track: Question Answering, Textual Inference, Language Understanding

Monash University

SECOND AUTHOR

June. 2020

• Under review in COLING 2020

Honors & Awards _____

2020	Data61 Project Winner, CSIRO Undergraduate Vacation Scholarships CSIRO	Dutton Park, Australia
2019	Highly Commended Undergraduate, Dean's Honours List UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia
2019	Taste of Research Winner, Taste of Research Scholarships UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia

Service _____

2020 Volunteer (Zoom Host), WiNLP 2020

Seattle, WA